Guide to the Jerome H. Holland papers, 1953-1985
Holland, Jerome H. papers, 1953-1985
- Series I. Professional Files
  - Mobile Oil Corporation, 1978-1986 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Monroe County Human Relations Commission, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Moorehouse College, 1968-1981 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - N: General, 1942-1975 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - N: General, 1976-1983, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - National Advisory Council on Health Research Facilities: Division of Educational and Research Facilities, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - National Advisory Council on Health Research Facilities: Division of Educational and Research Facilities, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - National Advisory Council on Health Research Facilities: Division of Educational and Research Facilities, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - National Advisory Council on Health Research Facilities: NIH, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - National Advisory Council on Health Research Facilities: NIH, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - National Art Museum of Sport, 1966-1969, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People: Annual Dinner Address, April 13, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People: Correspondence, 1964-1984 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People: Remarks to the N.A.A.C.P. of Central Delaware, May 6, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People: Tenth Annual Dinner Dance, April 29, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - National Association of Investment Clubs, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - National Citizens Committee for Public Television, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association, 1960-1973 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association: Select Committee on Athletic Problems and Concerns in Higher Education, 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1952-1955 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1967-1970 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1976-1979 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1980-1984 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews: Howard Goldfelder Award Dinner, February-March 1981 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews: Knoxville, Tennessee Chapter, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews: Wichita, Kansas Chapter, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - National Conference on Philanthropy, 1979, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - National Football Foundation and Hall of Fame, 1951-Fe. 1965 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - National Football Foundation and Hall of Fame, Feb. 15 1965-June 1965 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - National Football Foundation and Hall of Fame, October 1965-Dec. 1969 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - National Football Foundation and Hall of Fame, 1973-1984 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - National Football Foundation and Hall of Fame: Induction, Cornell-Princeton Half-time, October 9, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - National Football Foundation and Hall of Fame: Tournament of the Roses, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - National Foundation on the Arts and the Humanities, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - National Geographic Society, 1977-1980 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - National Geographic Society, 1981-1984 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - National Geographic Society: Middle East Trip, June-August 1978 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - National Insurance Association, 1966, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - National Medical Fellowships, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - National Medical Fellowships, 1968-June 1969 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - National Medical Fellowships, Sept. 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - National Medical Fellowships, 1972-1976 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - National Merit Scholarship Corporation, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - National Merit Scholarship Corporation, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - National Safety Council, 1967-1969 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - National Study of American College and University Presidents, Michigan State College, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - National Symphony Orchestra, 1973-1982 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - National Urban League, 1944-1959 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - National Urban League, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - National Urban League, 1961-1965 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - National Urban League, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - National Urban League, 1973-1984 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - National Voluntary Social Service Advisory Council, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - NEA Journal (Journal of the National Education Association), March 1965 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Negro Athlete Hall of Fame, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Netter, Richard, 1975-1985 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - New Directions, 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - New York Chamber of Commerce and Industry, and Economic Development Council, 1974-1981 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - New York Hospital: Cornell Medical Center, 1975-1984, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - New York Stock Exchange, 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - New York Stock Exchange, 1975-1978 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - New York Stock Exchange, 1979-1984, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - New York Stock Exchange: James J. Needham, 1973-1977 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - New York Telephone, 1947, 1973-1981 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - New York Telephone bills for residence, 1983-1985 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - New York University: Alumni Association, 1973-1974, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - New York Urban League, 1973, 1978, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Nixon, Richard, 1973-1974, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Noble, Leary & Leary: Mrs. Lydia Mosley, 1946 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Nordberg Fellowship Fund, 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Norfolk, Proposed bank, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - North American Association of Summer Sessions, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Northeastern University, May-July 1965 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - O: General, 1941-1982 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Office of War Mobilization, 1944-1945 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Ohio Bell, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Ohio Board of Regents, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Ohio Northern University, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Old Dominion Foundation Fellowship Program, 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Omega Psi Phi Fraternity, Inc., 1962-1967 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Overseas Business Associates, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - P: General, 1941-1982, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Pan American Bancshares: Audit Committee, 1977-1979 (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Pan American Bancshares, 1973-1984 (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Peninsula Chamber of Commerce: Honorary Director, 1968-1970 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Pew, J. Howard, 1947-1969 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Pew, Jno G., 1952-1969 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Pew, John G., 1945-1964 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Pew, Joseph N., Jr., 1945-1951 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Pew, Joseph N., Jr., 1952 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Pew, Joseph N., Jr., 1953-1967, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Pew, Walter C. Sr., December 1964 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Pew Memorial Foundation, 1951-1983, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Ph.D. Term Papers, 1918, 1941-1946, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Ph.D. Thesis, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Phelps Stokes Fund, 1975-1981 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Phoenix Urban League, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Physical Fitness Leadership Awards, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Pierce, Samuel R., Jr., 1981 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Pigskin Club, 1954-1959 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Pigskin Club, 1960-1970 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Pittsburg Urban League, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Center for Family Planning program development, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Center for Family Planning program development, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Center for Family Planning program development, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, Jan. 1968 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, Feb.-Mar. 1968 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, Apr.-June 1968 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, July-Aug. 1968 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, Sept. 1968 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, Oct.-Nov.19, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, Nov.20-30, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, Dec. 1968 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, Jan.1-14, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, Jan.15-31, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, Feb.3-9, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, Feb.10-28, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, Mar. 1-20, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, Mar. 21-31, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, Apr. 1-19, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, Apr. 20-30, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, May 1-22, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, May 23-28, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, June 1969 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, July 1969 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, Aug. 1969 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, Sept. 1969 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, Sept. 1969 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, Oct.1-26, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, Oct.27-31, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, Nov. 1969 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, Dec. 1969 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, Jan. 1970 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, Jan.2-9, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, Jan.12-19, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, Jan.20-Mar.ch, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, Jan.20-Mar.ch, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Correspondence, 1973-1982 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Data, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Data, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Data, Sept. 1968 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Data, Sept. 1969 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Data, Sept. 1969 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Data, Sept. 1969 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Data, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Hampton Institute Student Chapter, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Peninsula area, 1966-1968 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population: Peninsula area, 1969-1970 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Plans for Progress Conference, Nov. 2, 1965, 1966-1968 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Plans for Progress Conference, Nov. 2, 1965: Dr. Holland's speech (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Population Crisis, 1969-1976 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Population Reference Bureau, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - President's Commission on Olympic Sports, 1975-1978 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - President's Commission on Olympic Sports: Expenses, 1975-1977 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - President's Commission on White House Fellowships, 1982-1984 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - President's International Youth Exchange Initiative, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Presidential Classroom for Young Americans, 1979-August 1980 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Prince Hall Grand Lodge: Free Masons, 1961-1983 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Princess Anne College, Maryland, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Princeton University: Advisory Council to Department of Sociology, 1974-1977 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Public Health Services National Advisory Council on Health Research Facilities, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Quotes, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - R: General, 1944-1983 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - R.J. Reynolds Industries, 1973, 1979-1982 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Ralph Bunche Memorial, 1976, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Religion in American Life, Inc., 1975-1979 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Religion in American Life, Inc., 1980 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Religion in American Life, Inc., 1981-1983 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Research Documents on Race, 1952-1954 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Rider College, 1974-1976 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Robert R. Moton Memorial Institute, Center for Independent Studies, 1975-1976, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1963, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1952-1978 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Rockefeller University Council, 1973-1979 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - R.R. Donnelley & Sons Company, 1973-1984 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Runnymede Corporation, 1965-1975 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - S: General, 1944-1974 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - S: General, 1975-1984, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Saint Augustine's College, 1955-1964 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Saint Augustine's College, 1972-1984 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Saint Paul's College, 1959-1965 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Saint Paul's College, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Saint Paul's College, 1975-1982 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Saint Philomena's Home and Community Center, Durban, South Africa, 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Salvation Army: Annual Luncheon, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Salvation Army: Association of Greater Boston Annual Banquet, May 20, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Salvation Army award, 1967-Nov. 1968 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Salvation Army award, Dec.1-6, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Salvation Army award, Dec.7, 1968-1970 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Salvation Army: Clippings, photographs, and miscellaneous, 1968-1981, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Salvation Army: Correspondence, 1969-1983, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Salvation Army: 100th Anniversary, March 10, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Sarnoff, R. W., 1972-1976 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Save the Children Federation, 1973-1983 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Scandinavian World Trade Center AB, February-April 1973 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Scholar assistance, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - School-Within-A-School and miscellaneous, 1973-1975 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Shafqat, Ambassador and family, 1973, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Select Committee on Athletic Problems and Concerns in Higher Education, 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Selective Services, 1943-1945 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Shimer College, 1973, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Sierra Leone project, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Sierra Leone project, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Sierra Leone project, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Sierra Leone project, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - Sierra Leone project, 1964-1965, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - Sierra Leone project: Newspaper clippings, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - Sierra Leone project: Preliminary surveys, 1959-1960 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Skelleffed, Kommun, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Smith, John (money manager, Sataur Capital), 1974 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Society of the New York Hospital, 1973-1984 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Solomon Fuller Institute, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Southern Illinois University at Carbondale, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Southern Tier Banking Association: Ithaca, NY, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Southwest Missouri State University, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Southwest Missouri State University, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Southwest Missouri State University: 6th Annual Insurance Day, November 1983 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Speech: AME Church, Dover, Deleware, February 28, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Speech: AME Church, Millsboro, Deleware, October 26, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Speech: Admissions Officers of the College & Universities of the New England States, June 12, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Speech: Agricultural Extension Service of Virginia Polytechnic Institute, September 2, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Speech: Akron Community Service Center and Urban League, Inc., February 20, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Speech: Aldersgate Methodist Church, February 7, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Speech: Alpha Kappa Mu Honor Society, March 26-28, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Speech: American Association of College & University Business Officers, Atlanta, GA, May 7, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Speech: American Association of University Professors, Ithaca, NY, April 28, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Speech: American Association of University Women, Dover, Delaware, October 17, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Speech: American Association of University Women, Milwaukee, WI, 1967-1969 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Speech: American Management Association, October 7, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Speech: Arctic Roofing Company, Wilmington, Delaware, April 3, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Speech: Armstrong High School, Richmand, Virginia, June 9, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Speech: "As Others See Us" or "The Mirror of America", January-February 1973 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Speech: Audio-Visual Leadership Conference, Tarrytown, NY, January 21-23, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Speech: Bancroft School, Wilmington, Delaware, April 10, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Speech: Benjamin Franklin High School, July 5, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Speech: Beth Emeth Congregation, Wilmington, Delaware, May 16, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Speech: A Better Chance Program, 10th Anniversary Celebration, April 1974 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Speech: Bridgeville School #220, June 5, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Speech: Brotherhood Day Remarks, February 21, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Speech: Brotherhood Meeting, Massapequa, NY, February 19, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Speech: Brotherhood Program, West Chester, PA, February 21, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Speech: Brown, Walter A. funeral services, July 22, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Speech: Business Executives of the Philadelphia Area, May 1, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Speech: Canton Urban League, OH, February 19, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Speech: Centennial Fund Campaign Luncheon, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Speech: Chapel of the Four Chaplains, Accepting the Freedom Citation, March 2 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Speech: Citizens of the St. Louis Area, March 9, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Speech: Classroom Teachers' Association of the National Education Association, July 11, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Speech: Clyde High School, June 8, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Speech: Coatsville Banquet for Baseball Players, December 6, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Speech: College Language Association, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Speech: College Presidents and Executives Conference, January 10-11, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Speech: Columbus Urban League Guild, Columbus, OH, April 30, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Speech: Commonwealth Club, Cincinnati, OH, November 12, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Speech: Community Presbyterian Church, March 17, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Speech: Dayton, Ohio Urban League, Equal Opportunity Day Program, November 20, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Speech: Delaware Congress of Parents and Teachers, Seaford, Delaware, May 3, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Speech: Delaware State Chamber of Commerce, Wilmington, Delaware, February 10, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Speech: Delaware State Teachers' Association Meeting, December 10, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Speech: Dover Council of Church Women, May 9, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Speech: Dunleith Community School, Wilmington, Delaware, February 12, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Speech: Easton Star Lodge No. 16 Free and Accepted Masons, Easton, Maryland, March 23, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Speech: Ellston High, June 10, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Speech: Farleigh Dickinson University, Student-Faculty Convocation, March 29, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Speech: Federation of Women's Clubs of Virginia, June 25, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Speech: Florida Agricultural and Mechanical University, August 7, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Speech: George Washington Carver High School, Elkton, Maryland, June 10, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Speech: Governor's Conference on Human Rights and Opportunities, Hartford, CT, March 30, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Speech: Governor's Conference on Manpower Training, Buffalo, NY, June 3, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Speech: Governor's Council of Executives and Directors of State Agencies, Dover, Delaware, April 30, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - Speech: Guidance Institute, July 17, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Speech: Howard High School Basketball Team, May 1, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - Speech: Howard University Centennial Program, February 28, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - Speech: Hughes, Langston Presentation, February 5, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - Speech: Iota Mu Chapter of Kappa Delta Pi, Hampton, Virginia, February 8, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - Speech: Jamtland Reserve Officer's Club, "International Relations and its Meaning to the Reserve Officers" (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - Speech: John L. McGriff Dental Society, Norfolk, VA, June 18, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 69)
  - Speech: John Wesley Methodist Church, Seaford, Delaware, October 27, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 70)
  - Speech: Kearney Foundation, Milwaukee, WI, December 8, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 71)
  - Speech: Kent County Educational Association's Annual Meeting, Dover, Delaware, March 9, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 72)
  - Speech: King, Dr. Martin Luther Memorial Services, April 5, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 73)
  - Speech: King, Dr. Martin Luther Jr., In Memory, Massachussettes Institute of Technology, January 13, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 74)
  - Speech: Kiwanis Club of Racine, Wisconsin, "The American Business Scene: As Viewed from Outside U.S.A.", March 28, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 75)
  - Speech: Lake Street Methodist Church, Middletown, Delaware, October 23, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 76)
  - Speech: Laymen's Midyear Conference, Delaware Conference of the Methodist Church, December 7, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 77)
  - Speech: Lewis Redding School, March 21, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 78)
  - Speech: Lion's Club, Wilmington, Delaware, December 1, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 79)
  - Speech: Maxwell Club Luncheon, Philadelphia, PA, October 31, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 80)
  - Speech: Medical, Dental & Pharmaceutical Society Dinner, March 31, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 81)
  - Speech: Men of Cliveden Annual Award Dinner, January 24, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 82)
  - Speech: Methodist Church, Laurel, Delaware, February 9, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 83)